{
    "id": "b8bf4dbae3ac478882376ddc995f8fc0",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The girl .................................... answered the phone was quite polite.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people and which to refer to things. When the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause we use who.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman ...................................... lives next door is an artist.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people and which to refer to things. When the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause we use who.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the man ...................................... ordered the cab?",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people and which to refer to things. When the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause we use who.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have lost the paper on ...................................... I had written his address.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The day ............................................ I met her is the happiest day of my life.",
            "description": "When can mean on which.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "on which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The man .............................................. interviewed me was quite helpful.",
            "description": "That can refer to people in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got four dogs all of ................................................... are quite friendly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You should talk to the people ........................................... placed this order.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people and which to refer to things. When the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause we use who.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The driver ....................................... caused the accident was arrested.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people and which to refer to things. When the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause we use who.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The police arrested the man ......................................... had stolen the jewels.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people and which to refer to things. When the relative pronoun is the subject of the relative clause we use who.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ....................................... leg is broken is sitting there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who's",
                "whose",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}